Guide to the Samuel Shaffer papers, 1948-1982 MS2091
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Chronological files, 1948-1976; MS2091 Series 1; 17 Linear feet
  - Chronological files, 11/16/1969-11/30/1969 (Box 24, Folder 6)
    [from original finding aid] Haynsworth (11/20/69)(Nov 20 1969); Haynsworth Correction (A Minor Correction in my Haynsworth file:) (Nov 21 1969); Add Haynsworth (11/21/69)(Nov 21 1969) Haynsworth (11/21/69)(Nov 21 1969); Further add Haynsworth (11/21/69)(Nov 21 1969); Haynsworth (add Senate reaction)(Nov 21 1969); Add Haynsworth (11/21/69); Correction (11/22/69)(First take Haynsworth); Taxes (11/26/69)(Nov 26 1969)
  - Chronological files, 12/0l/1969-12/15/1969 (Box 24, Folder 7)
    [from original finding aid] Violin (taxes)(12/3/69)(Dec 4 1969); Add Violin (taxes)(12/5/69)(Dec 5 1969); Congress Week--Take One (The Vietnam resolution)(12/5/69)(Dec 5 1969); Haynsworth (51st vote)(Dec 11 1969); Congress Week (12/11/69) Add Voting Rights (Dec 12 1969); Further add Voting Rights Martha Mitchell (Dec 12 1969); Congress Advisory (Dec 1969); Add Taxes, 12-12-69 (Dec 12 1969) Add Violin (Dec 12 1969); Add Violin (12/12/69)(Dec 12 1969)
  - Chronological files, 12/16/1969-12/31/1969 (Box 24, Folder 8)
    [from original finding aid] Congress (12/18/69)(Dec 18 1969); Congress-Take Two (12/18/69)(Dec 18 1969); Congress Roundup (12/23/69)(Dec 23- 1969); Tax bill and politics (12/19/69)(Dec 19 1969); Congress--take three (12/19/69)(Dec 19 1969); Add to tax and politics (12/19/69)(Dec 19 1969); Add Congress (12/24/69)(Dec 19 1969); Correction (12/27/69)(N14 Congress)(Dec 27 1969)
  - Chronological files, 01/1970 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    [from original finding aid] Congress (1/15/70)(Jan 15 1970); Nixon Review, takelll (Jan 15 1970); Congress Week (1/22/70)(Jan 22 1970); Carswell (1/22/70)(Jan 22 1970); No-knock (1/29/70)(Jan 29 1970); Veto (1/29/70)(Jan 29 1970); Add Veto file (1/30/70)(Jan 30 1970)
  - Chronological files, 02/0l/1970-02/15/1970 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    [from original finding aid] Budget- Congress reaction (1/5/70)(Feb 5 1970); Add Viet/ABM (1/5/70)(Feb 5 1970); Vietnam/ABM (1/5/70)(Feb 5 1970); Add Viet/ABM File (1/6/70)(Feb 6 1970); Democratic Budget Reaction (1/6/70)(Feb 6 1970); Congress--school bill (21/11/70)(Feb 11 1970); Add to Congress/school file (2/12/70)(Feb 12 1970); Further add Congress/school file (1/12/70)(Feb 12 1970); One more further add Congress (2/12/70)(Feb 12 1970); Query #8 (Stennis amendment); Correction (Feb 14 1970)(N17 Violin)(Feb 14 1970); N17 Violin (Feb 14 1970)
  - Chronological files, 02/16/1970-02/28/1970 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    [from original finding aid] Congress-school fight (2/19/70)(Feb 19 1970); State of World (Congressional reaction)(Feb 19 1970); Panetta (2/20/70)(Feb 20 1970); HEW money bill (2/20/70)(Feb 20 1970); ABM/Congress-- (2/25/70)(Feb 25 1970); Laos and the Senate (2/26/70)(Feb 26 1970)
  - Chronological files, 03/0l/1970-03/15/1970 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    [from original finding aid] Violin: Congress: Voting rights and the HEW money bill (3/5/70)(Mar 5 1970); Congress: HEW money bill (3/5/70)(Mar 5 1970); Add Violin/Congress (3/6/70)(Mar 6 1970); Further add violin/Congress (3/6/70)(Mar 6 1970); Last add (hopefully) Violin (3/6/70)(Mar 6 1970); Voting rights (3/12/70)(mar 12 1970); Add Voting rights (3/12/70)(Mar 13 1970); Laos/Congress (3/13/70)(Mar 13 1970)
  - Chronological files, 03/l6/1970-03/31/1970 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    [from original finding aid] Carswell (3/19/70)(Mar 19 1970); To Biz, from Shaffer (FI??)(Mar 20 1970)(Ford); Bombing (Mar 20 1970); Correction (3/21/70) War and Copy Desk from Shaffer; Brumley Defrank Wash (W13 Laos)(Mar21 1970); Corrections (3/21/70) Nation Howard from Shaffer; Defrank Wash (N13 Carswell)(Mar 21 1970); N13 Carswell (Mar 21 1970); Carswell (3/25/70)(Nomination to Supreme Court); Tally Sheet (Mar 25 1970); School Message (3/26/70)(Mar 26 1970); Add Carswell (3/26/70)(Mar 26 1970)
  - Chronological files, 04/1970 (Box 25, Folder 6)
    [from original finding aid] Carswell-Take I (04/2/1970); Add Carswell (Take II)(04/3/1970); Carswell (4/9/70)(04/9/1970); Add Carswell (4/10/70)(04/10/1970); Further add Carswell (4/10/70)(04/10/1970); Correction (4/11/70)(N14 Carswell)(04/11/1970); Blackman (4/16/70)(04/16/1970); Blackman react (04/16/1970); Correction (N15 New Senate) 04/18/1970; Draft reform (04/23/1970) (04/23/1970); Troops/Cambodia; Add Cambodia; Carswell; Cambodia/Congress
  - Chronological files, 05/1970 (Box 25, Folder 7)
    [from original finding aid] Cambodia/Congress--Take II (5/1/70) (May 1 1970); Cambodia/Congress (5/7/70)(May 7 1970); Correction (May 9 1970)(N13 Congress); Nation Montagno Shaffer Wash (Mcgovern-Hatfield-Goodell; Hughes-Cranston amendment); Nation and copydesk Shaffer Wash (your questions on N13 Congress)(May 9 1970); Violin (Congress and the constitutional confrontation)--5/14/70 Take III (May 14 1970); Add Violin (5/15/70)(May 15 1970) Cooper-Church (5/21/70)(May 21 1970); Add Cooper-Church (5/21/70)(May 22 1970) Senate/Cambodia (5/27/70)(May 27 1970)
  - Chronological files, 06/0l/1970-06/15/1970 (Box 25, Folder 8)
    [from original finding aid] Margaret Smith (6/3/70)(Margaret Chase Smith and McCarthy)(Jun 4 1970); Nixon- Take II (6/4/70)(Jun 4 1970); Add Margaret Smith (6/5/70); To Kubic, Beirut via New York from Shaffer, Washington (Dr.John Adams); Cooper-Church (6/11/70)(Jun 11 1970); Penn Central (6/11/70)(Jun 11 1970)
  - Chronological files, 06/16/1970-06/30/1970 (Box 25, Folder 9)
    [from original finding aid] President's speech (6/18/70)(Jun 18 1970); Congress Week--6/18/70 (Voting Rules 18 yr old vote) (Jun 18 1970); Add Congress file (6/19/70)(Voting rights)(Jun 19 1970); Congress--cello (6/25/70)(Nixon/Week/Congress Take one)(Jun 25 1970); Penn-central (6/25/70) (Jun 25 1970); Add Congress (1/26/70)(Jun 26 1970)
  - Chronological files, 07/01/1970-7/17/1970 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    [from original finding aid] Cover--Congress (7/1/70)(Jul 1 1970); Veto--7/1/70 (Jul 1 1970); Congress-7/9/70 (Jul 9 1970); Add Congress--(7/10/70)(Jul 10 1970); Further add to Congress add (7/10/70)(Jul 10 1970); Douglas (7/9/70)(Jul 9 1970); Douglas-Take II (Cellar Quotes et al)(Jul 10 1970)
  - Chronological files, 07/18/1970-07/31/1970 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    [from original finding aid] My Lai report (7/16/70)(Jul 16 1970); Business-Martin/Moore Shaffer (add trade)(Jul 17 1970); Congress--ABM (7/30/70)(Jul 29 1970); With budget cello-(7/30/70)(Jul 29 1970); Add ABM (7/30/70)(Jul 30 1970); Congressional secrecy (7/30/70)-Take II (Jul 30 1970)
  - Chronological files, 08/1970-09/1970 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    [from original finding aid] Congressional Reform (Aug 1 1970); Contract awards ploy (8/6/70)(Aug 6 1970)(Pentagon Contract Awards); ABM--8/13/70 (Aug 13 1970); Media Shaffer, Washington (TV political bill) (Aug 14 19'70); Add ABM (8/14/70)(Aug 14 1970); Veto (with Nixon week)(Aug 20 1970); Tydings (8/20/70)(Aug 20 1970); Gas Treaty (8/20/70)(Aug 20 1970); Conway from Shaffer (Aug 20 1970); Conway from Shaffer Wash.Star p.3 Aug 21; Conway from Shaffer (Aug 21 1970 )(Excerpt from Sen.; Robert Dole's speech) Query #3--military assistance to Cambodia, etc (8/21/70)(Aug 21 1970); Watson, Foreign, Shaffer, Washington (8/21/70)(Aug 21 1970); Congress--the rest of the doves (8/27/70)(Aug 27 1970) SST (8/27/70)(Aug 27 1970)
  - Chronological files, 10/1970 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    [from original finding aid] Violin (10/8/70)(President's Speech)(Oct 8 1970); Add Politics-(Polls)(10/8/70)(Oct 8 1970); Violin (10/8/70)(Oct 8 1970)(Tydings); Query #2 (Oct 9 1970)(Goldwater); Query #3 (Oct 9 1970)(Fulbright); With Veto (10/15/70)(Oct 15 1970); Taiwan (Oct 15 1970); Congress Quits (10/15/70)(Oct 15 1970); Add Congress (10/16/70)(Oct 16 1970); Corrections (Oct 17 1970)(N14 Congress); Violin (10/21/70)(Oct 21 1970)(Voter Apathy)
  - Chronological files, 11/01/1970-11/15/1970 (Box 26, Folder 5)
    [from original finding aid] Violin--Senate (11/5/70)(Nov 5 1970); Violin (11/11/70)(Nov 11 1970)(lame ducks); Add violin (Nov 12 1970)(McGovern); Senate whip race (Nov 12 1970); Further add violin (11/12/70)(Nov 13 1970)(Lame duck); Correction (11/14/70)(N16 Violin)(Nov 14 1970); Congress returns (11/19/70)(Nov 19 1970); Add Congress (11/20/70)(Nov 20 1970); Further add Congress (Nov 20 1970); With violin (Nov 20 1970)(Mills); Further, further add violin (11/20/70)(Nov 20 1970); Correction (11/21/70)(N16 Lame duck); With trade (11/25/70)(Nov 25 1970); TV veto (11/25/70)(Nov 25 1970)
  - Chronological files, 11/16/1970-11/30/1970 (Box 26, Folder 6)
    [from original finding aid] SST (12/10/70)(Dec 3 1970); Congress Week (12/10/70)(Dec 10 1970); Add Congress (12/11/70); Add Bush; In re Congress Week-(Dec 14 1970); Congress (12/12/70)(Dec 17 1970); Nation, Kosner, Auchinloss, Shaffer, Washington (Dec 17 1970)(radio?)(Dec 17 1970)(Connally); Add Congress (12/18/70)(Dec 18 1970); TFX (Dec 18 1970); Cello--Congress (12/22/70)(Dec 22 1970); Violin (12/29/70)(Dec 29 1970) Add violin (12/30/70)(Dec 30 1970); Add violin (12/30/70)(Dec 30 1970)(Welfare reform)
  - Chronological files, 01/01/1971-01/15/1971 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    [from original finding aid] Congress Cover (1/6/70); Most Powerful Senators (Jan 12 1971); Roeder from Shaffer (Jan 12 1971)(Senator Byrd); Add Cover (Jan 13 1971); Congress Cover Query (Jan 13 1971); Further Add Cover (Jan 14 1971)
  - Chronological files, 01/16/1971-01/31/1971 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    [from original finding aid] Cambodia (1/20/71)(Jan 21 1971); Richard Russell (Jan 21 1971); Byrd box (1/22/71); Correction (1/22/71)(My No.12 of today slugged Congress)(Jan 22 1971); Congress (1/22/71)(Jan 22 1971) State of Union address (1/22/71)(Jan 22 1971); Correction (1/23/71)(N12 Russell)(Jan 23 1971); Violin (Cambodia/Congress)(Jan 28 1971); Klein from Shaffer (Add Violin-Congress)(Jan 28 1971); Filibuster rule (1/28/70)(Jan 28 1971); Dove reaction to possible Laos invasion (1/29/71)(Jan 29 1971); With cello (1/28/71)(Jan 29 1971)(Nixon)
  - Chronological files, 02/0l/1971-02/17/1971 (Box 27, Folder 3)
    [from original finding aid] Biz, Martz (also media) Connally (2/3/71 (Feb 3 1971); Intro-Union? (Congress)(Feb 3 1971)(Indochina); Add Connally (2/3/71)(Feb 3 1971); Add Indochina (3/2/71)(Feb 4 1971); Add cover file--Indochina (Feb 5 1971); Laos/Congress (2/11/71)(Feb 11 1971); Add Tick-Tock (2/11/71)(Feb 11 1971); Jerry Ford (2/11/71)(Feb 12 1971); Correction (2/13/71)(N16 Ford)(Feb 13 1971)
  - Chronological files, 02/18/1971-02/28/1971 (Box 27, Folder 4)
    [from original finding aid] Filibuster (2/18/71)(Feb 18 1971); Mundt (2/18/71)(Feb 18 1971); Health care (2/19/71)(Feb 19 1971); Humphrey and the President (2/19/71)(Feb 19 1971); With violin (2/19/71)(Feb 19 1971); Add violin (2/19/71)(Feb 19 1971); Biz, Martz, Shaffer, Washington with? Leader? (2/25/71); (Feb 5 1971)(Wage-price controls/suspending the; Bacon-Davis Act) With Laos story-(Feb 25 1971) Laos/Congress (2/25/71)(Feb 25 1971); Casey nomination (2/26/71)(Feb 26 1971)
  - Chronological files, 03/1971 (Box 27, Folder 5)
    [from original finding aid] Agnew (3/11/71)(Mar 11 1971); Congress Week (3/11/71)(Mar 11 1971); For the Violin (3/11/71)(Mar 11 1971); Auchinloss, Peri, Shaffer (Violin)(Nixon;SST); Nation, Kosner, Shaffer, with SST (Letter to Honorable; Margaret Chase Smith) SSt (3/2.5/71)(jlar .25 1971); Kosner, Alpern from Shaffer (Acid SST ) (Mar 25 1971); Add SSt (3/25/71)(Mar 25 1971); Violin (3/26/71)(Mar 26 1971); Violin (3/26/71)(Mar 26 1971); J.Edgar Hoover and Congress (Mar 31 1971)
  - Chronological files, 04/1971 (Box 27, Folder 6)
    [from original finding aid] Violin (3/31/71)(Apr 1 1971) (Lt. William Galley); Add Violin (4/1/71)(Apr 1 1971)(Galley); Further add violin (04/01/71)(Congressional mood; Congress); Cello--Vietnam/Congress (04/07/71)(Apr 7 1971); Add cello--post speech (01/08/71)(Apr 8 1971); Further add cello--Vietnam/Congress (04/08/71)(Apr 8 1971); International/Klein Shaffer/Wash April 15 (Congress Reaction-)(April 15 1971); Busing--the school aid bill (04/21/71); Demonstrations-Congress and the war (4.21/71)(Apr 21 1971); Add busing (04/26/71) (Apr 22 1971); The economy (4/23/71) (Apr 23 1971); Query #1 ribicoff (04/22/71) (Apr 22 1971); Senate (4/2W/71) (Apr 27 1971) (J. Edgar Hoover); Newsweek Features, Shep Campbell, Shaffer, Washington (FBI statistics)(04/29/71)(Apr 29 1971) FBI (Apr 29 1971)(J.Edgar Hoover)
  - Chronological files, 05/1971 (Box 27, Folder 7)
    [from original finding aid] Draft debate (5/5/71)(May 5 1971); Demos (Congress)(May 5 1971); Biz, Martz, Shaffer, Washigton (Lockheed)(5/6/71); Draft (5/12/71)(May 12 1971); Add draft (5/13/71)(May 13 1971); More violin (5/14/71)(May 14 1971)(Mansfield amendment); Further add violin (4/14/71)(May 14 1971)(Griffin;; Mansfield amendment); New Violin (5/14/71)(May 14 1971)(Mansfield); Add draft (5/14/71)(May 14 1971)(Mansfield); Violin (Mansfield)-5/19/71 (May 19 1971); N18 Mansfield (May 21 1971); Bernstein/Kosner (May 25 1971) from Shaffer (May 25 1971)(Kissinger) Draft (5/26/71)(May 26 1971)
  - Chronological files, 06/1971 (Box 27, Folder 8)
    [from original finding aid] Add Congress (6/2/71)(revenue sharing); Congress Week (6/2/71)(Jun 2 1971); Query #2 (F-14)--6/2/71 (Jun 2 1971); Add draft (6/3/71); Violin--cops/White House (6/3/71)(Jun 3 1971); Pay raise (6/10/71)(Jun 10 1971); Violin (6/10/71) Take one (Jun 10 1971)(military draft); Add violin (6/11/71)(Jun 11 1917)(Draft); McGovern-Hatfield (6/17/71)(Jun 18 1971); Further add McGovern-Hatfield (6/8/71)(Jun 18 1971); Add McGovern-Hatfield (6/17/71); Revenue sharing--6/21/71 (Jun 2 1971); Secrets (6/24/71)(Jun 24 1971); With violin (Congress)(6/24/71)(Jun 24 1971); Mansfield amendment (6/23/71)(Jun 24 1971); Add Mansfield amendment (6/25/71)(Jun 25 1971); Correction (6/26/71)(N16 Mansfield); Draft (6/30/71)(Jun 20 and 30 1971)
  - Chronological files, 07/01/1971-07/15/1971 (Box 28, Folder 1)
    [from original finding aid] Add to draft/gravel (Jul 1 1971); Add draft (6/30/71); Add draft (7/1/71)(Jul 1 1971); Peace Talks-Congress (Jul 1 1971); Add congressional reaction to VC offer (7/1/71)(Jul 1 1971); Correction (7/2/71)(W10 Peace Tape 2); Peace Offer (7/2/71)(Jul 2 1971); Proxmire? Advisory? (7/8/71)(Jul 8 1971); With Violin (7/8/71)(Jul 8 1971)(peace negotiations); Draft/gravel (7/8/71)(Jul 8 1971); With violin (7/9/71)(Jul 9 1971)(Vietnam); With Violin (7/15/71)(Jul 15 1971)(draft-extension bill); Cover (Jul 16 1971)(China)
  - Chronological files, 07/16/1971-07/31/1971 (Box 28, Folder 2)
    [from original finding aid] SACB (7/22/71)(Jul 22 71); With Violin (7/22/71)(China) Agnew (7/22/71)(Jul 22 1971); Congress (7/22/71)(Jul 22 1971); Correction (7/24/71)(N16 Board)(Jul 24 1971); Congress/Lockheed (7/29/71)(Jul 29 1971)(Take I); Further add Lockheed (7/30/71)(Jul 30 1971) Further, further add Lockheed (7/30/71)(Jul 30 1971); Further, further, further add Lockheed (7/30/71) Draft (7/30/71)(Jul 30 1971)
  - Chronological files, 02/01/1971-02/17/1971 (Box 28, Folder 3)
    [from original finding aid] Congress (8/4/71)(Aug 5 1971); Lockheed (8/4/71)(Aug 5 1971); With Violin and ? (8/4/71)(Aug 5 1971); Add violin (8/5/71)(Aug 6 1971)(wage-price guidelines); Lindsay (8/12/71)(Aug 12 1971); Violin (Congress)(7/19/71)(Aug 19 1971); Meany/Congress (also Violin)(Aug 26 1971); Busing (8/26/71)(Aug 26 1971); Congress (9/1/71)(Sep 1 1971)
  - Chronological files, 02/18/1971-02/28/1971 (Box 28, Folder 4)
    [from original finding aid] Violin--Nixon trip to Russia (10/14/71)(Oct 14 1971); Robert Byrd (Oct 14 1971); Byrd (10/15/71)(Oct 15 1971); Supreme Court (10/15/71)(Oct 15 1971); Nation from Shaffer (10/15/71)(Court)(Oct 15 1971); Mansfield amendment (10/21/71)(Oct 21 1971); Add Scotus (10/21/71)(Oct 22 1971); Further add Scotus (10/22/71)(Oct 22 1971); Cover (10/28/71)(Oct 28 1971)(UN's expulsion of Taiwan); Cover story and Cooper/Church amendment (Oct 29 1971); Mitchell/Congress (10/28/71)(Oct 28 1971); Cooper-Church (10/29/71)(Oct 29 1971); Foreign aid--violin-Take I (Oct 30 1971); Nation from Shaffer-10/30/71 (Violin-Take II)(Oct 30 1971); Nation from Shaffer -10/30/71 (Violin-Take IIl)(Oct 30 1971)
  - Chronological files, 03/1971 (Box 28, Folder 5)
    [from original finding aid] Ted Kennedy (11/4/71)(Nov 4 1971); Add Foreign aid (11/5/71)(Nov 5 1971) Foreign aid (11/4/71)(Nov 4 1971); Add foreign aid (11/12/71); Violin-reaction (11/12/71)(Nov 12 1971); Foreign aid (11/11/71); Congress--campaign spending (11/18/71)(Nov 18 1971); Kosner from Shaffer (11/18/71)(Warren Weaver; public; financing of Presidential elections) Troop withdrawal (11/19/71)(Nov 19 1971); Campaign Spending (11/19/71)(Nov 19 1971) Nation from Shaffer (11/19/71)(Nov 19 1971)(Warren Weaver; tax bill); Correction (11/20/71)(N18 Troops)(Nov 20 1971); Violin--Congress collision (11/24/71)(Nov 24 1971)
  - Chronological files, 04/1971 (Box 28, Folder 6)
    [from original finding aid] Violin--Congress (12/2/71)(Dec 2 1971); Add Violin (12/3/71)(Dec 3 1971); Congress--cello (12/9/71)(Dec 9 1971); Add Congress (12/10/71)(Dec 10 1971); Further add Congress (12/10/71); Congress (12/16/71)(Dec 18 1971)(Dec 18 1971); Add Congress (12/16/71)(Dec 16 1971); Indochina air war (1/6/72)
  - Chronological files, 01/1972 (Box 29, Folder 1)
    [from original finding aid] Congress (1/13/72)(Jan 13 1972) Correction (1/15/72)(Jan 14 1972)(N16 Union) State of Union--add Take IV (react)(Jan 20 1972); State of Union--the democratic response (1/21/72) (Jan 21 1972); Kosner from Shaffer (1/20/72)(Jan 20 1972)(Wallace's intentions); With violin (1/27/72)(Jan 27 1972)(Vietnam Negotiations) Cello/busing/Take I; Congress (1/27/72)(Jan 27 1972) Add to violin (1/28/72)(Jan 28 1972); Correction Nation (Holly Comp) and Copy Desk from Shaffer-1/29/72 (N23 Busing)
  - Chronological files, 02/1972 (Box 29, Folder 2)
    [from original finding aid] Mundt (2/3/72); Violin (welfare) 1/3/72 (Feb 3 1972); Muskie (Rogers(Feb 4 1972); Violin (Vietnam issue) 2/4/72 (Feb 4 1972); With Kleindienst (2/17/72)(Feb 17 1972); Busing (2/17/72)(Feb 17 1972); With violin (2/18/72)(Feb 18 1972)(Presidential trip; China); Violin--busing (2/24/72)(Feb 24 1972); Add Violin (2/25/72)(Feb 25 1972)(busing)
  - Chronological files, 03/1972 (Box 29, Folder 3)
    [from original finding aid] Busing (3/2/72)(Mar 2 1972); With Violin (3/2/72)(Mar 2 1972)(President's return from China); ITT (3/9/72)(Mar 9 1972) Busing (3/10/72)(Mar 10 1972); Kosner from Shaffer (3/16/72)(ITT); With violin (3/16/72)(Mar 16 1972)(Bayh's endorsement of Muskie for the Presidential nomination); Add violin (3/16/72)(presidential primaries); Violin (3/17/72)(Mar 17 1972)(Busing); Bob Wilson (3/20/72)(Mar 30 1972) Add Wilson (3/20/72) Equal rights (3/22/72); Violin (Congress react)(3/23/72)(Mar 23 1972)(pay); ITT (3/30 72)(Mar 30 1972); Violin-Congress (3/30/72)(Mar 30 1972)
  - Chronological files, 04/1972 (Box 29, Folder 4)
    [from original finding aid] Vietnam Cover (4/6/72)(Apr 6 1972); Cape Kennedy (4/6/72)(Apr 6 1972); Muskie (4/6/72)(Apr 6 1972); Add to Wisconsin (4/6/72)(Apr 6 1972); Add Wisconsin (4/7/72)(Apr 7 1972); Essay (Vietnam Response) 4/13/72 (Apr 13 1972); Add to essay-Vietnam (4/13/72)(Apr 13 1972); Kleindienst (4/13/72)(Apr 13 1972); Further add Kleindienst (4/14/72)(Apr 14 1972); Odd items (4/14/72)(Apr 14 1972); Correction (4/15/72) (N14 Powers) (Apr 15 1972); With Ervin (4/20/72) (Apr 20 1972); Violin (4/20/72) (Apr 20 1972) (Bombing of Hanoi and Haiphong); Add Kleindienst (4/21/72) (Apr 21 1972); With Violin-Senate (4/27/72) (Apr 27 1972)
  - Chronological files, 05/1972 (Box 29, Folder 5)
    [from original finding aid] Media, Morganstern, Shaffer, Washington (Congress/USIA)(5/4/72) (May 4 - 1972); With cover -- Vietnam/Congress (5/4/72) (May 4 1972); Welfare reform (5/5/72) (May 9 1972); Nation, Kosner, Auchincloss from Shaffer-excerpt from Mansfield report on trip to China (May 11 1972); Cello -- Vietnam/Congress ( 5/10/72 ) (May 11 1972); Add violin (5/l8/72) (May 18 1972 ) (Cellar ); With violin (Wallace) 5/18/72 (May 18 1972); Add Wallace (5/18/72)(May 18 1972); Congress (5/25/72); Cover/political implications (May 26 1972); Congress (updating earlier files) (May 31 1972)
  - Chronological files, 06/1972 (Box 29, Folder 6)
    [from original finding aid] Further update Congress (6/1/72) (Jun 1 1972); Query #12 -- 6/1/72 (Jun 1 1972 ) (Salt-Congress); Kleindienst (6/8|/72); Connally (6/8/72) (Jun 8 1972); With defense (Congress) (6/8/72 ) (Jun 8 1972); With McGovern- - the reaction in Congress (Jun 9 1972); Updating welfare (6/15/72 ) (Jun 15? 1972); Add Welfare (6/16/72 ) (Jun 18 1972); Further add welfare (6/16/72) (Jun 16 1972); Last add welfare (6/16/72 ) (Jun 16 1972); Lavelle case (6/15/72 ) (Jun 15 1972); #8 (Jun 22 1972)(Ellender); Abrams (6/22/72 ) (Jun 22 1972); Congress week- - revenue sharing (6/22/72 ) (Jun 22 1972); Congress/geriatricians (6/22/72 ) (Jun 22 1972); Query #4 (Jun 23 1972 ) (Troops ); Correction ( 6/24/72 ) (N14 Age); With violin (6/29/72 ) (Jun 29 1972 ) (Democrats); ADD violin (McGovern) 6/30/72 (Jun 30 1972)
  - Chronological files, 07/1972 (Box 29, Folder 7)
    [from original finding aid] Mitchell's resignation (7/1/72); Mitchell/Macgregor (7/5/72)(Jul 6 1972); Add Mitchell/Macgregor (7/5/72)(Jul 6 1972); Violin; With violin (Congress and teamsters)(Jul 20 1972)(Packwood-Teamsters) Agnew (7/22/72)(07/1972); Vietnam amendment (7/27/72)(Jul 27 1972); Eagleton/congressional reaction (7/27/72)(Jul 27 1972) GOP Eagleton react (7/28/72)(Jul 28 1972); Newsmakers, Roeder, Shaffer, Washington (Ellender 7/28/72)(Jul 28 1972)
  - Chronological files, 08/1972-09/1972 (Box 29, Folder 8)
    [from original finding aid] Nation, Auchincloss, Shaffer, Washington, (8/4/72)(Aug 4 1972); (Vice presidential nominee possibilities) Schmitz (8/4/72)(Aug 4 1972); Arms race (8/10/72)(Aug 10 1972) Schmitz (8/10/72)(Aug 10 1972); Add arms race file (8/11/72)(Aug 11 1972); Congress Week (8/11/72)(Aug 11 1972) With Violin (8/17/72)(Aug 17 1972)(Shriver, Nixon); Add Violin (8/18/72)(Aug 18 1972)(Lawton Chiles) GAO sidebar (8/30/72)(Aug 30 1972); Newsmakers, Roeder, Shaffer, Washington (Colson memo(8/31/72)(Aug 31 1972)
  - Chronological files, 10/1972 (Box 29, Folder 9)
    [from original finding aid] Congress (10/12/72)(Oct 12 1972); Senate race roundup (10/18/72)(Oct 18 1972); Nader Congress Report (Oct 20 1972); Klein from Shaffer (10/20/72)(Oct 20 1972)(defoliants); Correction (10/21/72)(N12 Senate)(Oct 21 1972); Violin-Congress (10/27/72)(Oct 27 1972)
  - Chronological files, 11/1972 (Box 29, Folder 10)
    [from original finding aid] Picking up the pieces-Take I (Nov 2 1972)(Democratic Party); Picking up the pieces (11/2/72) TAKE II (Nov 3 1972); Congress/Watergate (11/2/72)(Nov 2 1972); Nixon and Congress (11/6/72)(Nov 6 1972); Chris Wren from Shaffer (11/7/72)(Democrats); Congress (11/9/72)(Nov 9 1972); Congress--Take II (11/9/72); Mrs.Smith (11/9/72)-Take I (Nov 9 1972); Congress--Take III (Nov 9 1972); Newsmakers, Michaud, Shaffer, Washington (Query #10/Dies; (ll/16/72)(Nov 16 1972) Richardson (11/22/72)(Nov 22 1972); Demos (labor)(11/22/72)(Nov 22 1972) Zumwalt (11/22/72)(Nov 24 1972); Reorganization (11/29/72)
  - Chronological files, 12/1972 (Box 29, Folder 11)
    [from original finding aid] [???wood] (12/7/72)(Dec 7 1972); Congressional reform (12/15/72)(Dec 15 1972); Congress preview (12/26/72)(Dec 26 1972); Add Congress preview (12/27/72)(Dec 27 1972); Second add Congress preview (12/27)(Dec 27 1972); Violin (12/29/72)(Dec 29 1972); Viet mood violin (12/27/72)(Congress Reaction)(Dec 27 1972); B-52 Non-critics (Dec 27 1972)
  - Chronological files, 01/01/1973-01/15/1973 (Box 30, Folder 1)